It has begun! It's the second edition of Kankokari to make friends in Abenonami!
Today's guest is Fujitarimu-chan from Iginari Talk!
She came to Japan yesterday! I'm Fujitarimuu! Nice to meet you!
It's almost the first time for me to talk to you like this, or at an event.
I'm in Yamagata quite often, so I can give you a chance to get to know each other.
I sometimes go on stage, but this is the first time for us to talk properly.
I'd be happy if we could be friends today!
I don't have any friends in my memory, so I'd really appreciate it if you could be my friend today.
Please!
Please use today's opportunity to become friends with me!
Today's project is, we are going to release a collaboration drink!
Yes, this project is located on the 4th floor of EVS
This is a collaboration project with Rooftop E-Garden!
You've done Tork, right?
We are collaborating so much!
Oh, you are collaborating a lot?
Yes, we are!
Yes, we are! Let's collaborate!
The collaboration will last for 5 days from December 21 to 25!
It's Christmas!
It's so Christmas!
My EVS event is going to be held here on 23rd.
I'll be there!
Really?
I'm going to be there!
It's just a rehearsal, but I'll be there!
I'll do it the next day!
Oh, my God!
That's amazing!
So, we've come up with an original drink hour together, and we'd like to present it to the manager now!
We are going to present it to the manager now!
Just like a college project!
This is Manager Suda of Roost E Garden.
Good morning.
Good afternoon.
Yes, so I would like to have Manager Suda take a look at our proposal.
Please do.
Okay, I'll start.
This way.
Wow, it's really good.
I'm really surprised.
I've just put all the things I like into this album.
I released an album called Yume no Kakera (Pieces of a Dream).
I released an album called Yume no Kakera (Fragments of a Dream), and one of the songs on it is called Float.
So the title is a mixture of the title of the song and the title of the album.
As for the drink, I just love caramel.
So I had caramel milk.
I also really love papioca from the bottom of my heart.
So I put papioca in it.
As for soft serve ice cream, I like coffee flavored ice cream the best.
So I put coffee in it.
I also put caramel sauce and Brulee chips.
I also put caramel sauce and brulee chips, which is a kind of burnt caramel that is often sprayed on top of the ice cream.
I also put a star shaped chocolate.
I have always had a habit of putting a star in my signature.
I love stars.
I love stars, so I came up with the idea of a dream float with my favorite things in it.
Thank you very much.
This will probably be ready soon.
Maybe the coffee soft serve could be ice cream instead of soft serve.
It could be ice cream or something.
Taste-wise, caramel products sell really well at my place.
I would be happy to make it happen.
Yes, please.
Then I would like to continue.
There are two things.
First of all, you have a face.
It's a face.
It's like the face you see on the vase in art class.
I see.
Didn't I have one of those?
Is this the face that fits so well?
Like, here is a vase and here looks like a vase.
It's like a trick.
Yes, there was.
No, there isn't.
I wanted to reproduce it.
This part is acerola.
And here it's fresh cream.
I had them make it for me.
That's your face!
Yes, sir.
What do you think?
It's very original.
It's a profile.
I need to practice a little more.
That's for sure.
I'll give it a shot.
That's great.
In case this doesn't work.
Yes, this one, too.
Maginot Cherry Tropicale in Tambourine Collection
Yes, sir.
The straw is green first.
I like melon soda.
Make it a melon soda.
Tapioca with colorful tapioca.Tapioca with colorful tapioca.
Also, there's a miracle, right?
Yes, sir.
Make this one red, cherries, this way.
Cherry, cherry guess.
Cherry, this sticker, cherries here.
Cherry itself is not in it.
Oh, I see.
I don't really like them.
The whole product is a cherry image.
So you can see the strokes.
Yes, that's right.
What do you think?
I think it's better this way.
It's more realizable.
It is, isn't it?
Heron soda.
Ice cream or something in a package.
Cream soda.
This one is more like
Vanilla or something.
Hebin ice cream and a straw.
Cherry blossoms, cherry blossom ice cream.
Definitely good over there, too.
And on the bottom.
Tapioca and
I'd rather have cherry blossoms in it.
From a photographic point of view
Isn't it pretty?
Is that okay?
It was just right away.
But maybe it's this way.
I thought of it right away.
What about the side?
Well, don't worry.
Try a little harder.
When it comes to burying this tapioca...
I knew it.
Fill it with just tapioca.
I'm good at that.
I'm good at it.
You know, when I was little
ball-like.
So you're talking about building goal pools in the country.
In case you're wondering, it's not without products like that.
I don't know... or maybe it's not a drink, it's more like a sweet.
Can I change it at all?
No, no, no, no.
As close as possible.
Okay, then.
Mr. Suga, we hope you'll make it into a product.
We wish you the best of luck.
Cheer up!
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
Bean bean bean.
Yes. So, I had Mr. Fuda take a look at it.
How was Yoo-chan?
She was biting off a lot.
He bit me off.
I was so surprised, and I thought that Jang-chan would have told me not to overdo it, so I was very impatient.
You really thought it through, didn't you?
I was really surprised.
If I can reproduce this, it will be great.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I was so surprised.
I thought I was being selfish. I put a lot of things into it.
That's why I'm so happy to hear that you think it can be done quickly.
I'm looking forward to seeing it.
Mr. Sasuda.
It's Mr. Sasuda, isn't it?
I was really surprised.
I'm working hard on this too.
Amazing.
It's like watching a medical drama, right?
You know, like watching a medical drama where the character says, "I can do it.
There are people who can do it.
There are.
It's like they never fail.
It's like watching someone who never fails.
That's true.
So, we just finished filming, but by the time this video is finished, the prototype will be completed.
I was surprised.
I would like to show it to you.
Here it is.
Please take a look.
Hello.
This is Amedanami from the radio.
Ichitorimichan.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Today I am Wakato Yasumori.
Ichitorimichan.
I'm Ichitrimychan.
What a surprise, the two of us have come up with a new drink.
Sparkle, sparkle, sparkle.
Cute.
What a surprise, we'll be representing you today, and we'll be having shihaftee.
Bye bye.
Thank you.
Thank you.Thank you.
Then shall we have it right away? I would like to drink the dream float that Abenonami came up with.
It looks so cute. It looks delicious.
I'll have it right away.
Delicious!
But I fell so hard.
Oh no!
Sorry, but it's so good!
The coffee is so rich.
And the tapioca is sticky and delicious!
I'll have a cup of coffee, then.
What was that?
Maji Cherry Blossom
Tropical
The Winter Collection.
The Wintern Marine Collection.
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Melon Soda
You can see some kind of color.
Oh, the ice cream is so delicious. I don't know what it tastes like, but I think it's really delicious and a wonderful collaboration.
Their drinks are delicious. Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Now I would like to return to the two people in the studio. Here you go!
Wow! You can recreate it like this?
You've done a great job on the face.
It's amazing. It's so cute.
They even recreated Sakurako in the middle.
There are three of them.
It's amazing. All of them were made.
This drink will be available at Beebe's Rooftop E-Garden on the 4th floor for 5 days from December 21 to 25.
Wow, Lily Fetherland on the 23rd!
Yes, but suddenly at the last minute in character.
Please come and visit us. Please do.
On December 23rd, I will be holding a release event for my first album "Yume no Kakera" here at inwind.
I look forward to seeing you there.
I love milk!